[{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6465c37bf3c94e5d47515a6f"
  },
  "nameshirt_": "Ride or Die",
  "shirt_path": {
    "front": "635a011245faa7887ac97fe8_1684390779426-621930667",
    "back": "635a011245faa7887ac97fe8_1684390779455-913765450"
  },
  "detail": "A shirt want to permission: true",
  "user_id": {
    "$oid": "635a011245faa7887ac97fe8"
  },
  "property": {
    "_type": "crew_",
    "color": "rgb(255,255,255)"
  },
  "permission": true,
  "shirtPrice": null
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6465c451f3c94e5d47515a83"
  },
  "nameshirt_": "ANARCHY",
  "shirt_path": {
    "front": "635a011245faa7887ac97fe8_1684390993678-516252035",
    "back": "635a011245faa7887ac97fe8_1684390993679-921007576"
  },
  "detail": "A shirt want to permission: true",
  "user_id": {
    "$oid": "635a011245faa7887ac97fe8"
  },
  "property": {
    "_type": "crew_",
    "color": "rgb(255,255,255)"
  },
  "permission": true,
  "shirtPrice": null
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6465c472f3c94e5d47515a87"
  },
  "nameshirt_": "SharkTank",
  "shirt_path": {
    "front": "635a011245faa7887ac97fe8_1684391026924-821485131",
    "back": "635a011245faa7887ac97fe8_1684391026933-228046896"
  },
  "detail": "A shirt want to permission: true",
  "user_id": {
    "$oid": "635a011245faa7887ac97fe8"
  },
  "property": {
    "_type": "crew_",
    "color": "rgb(255,255,255)"
  },
  "permission": true,
  "shirtPrice": null
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6465c4c8f3c94e5d47515a98"
  },
  "nameshirt_": "Wave I'm Coming",
  "shirt_path": {
    "front": "635a011245faa7887ac97fe8_1684391112566-45831964",
    "back": "635a011245faa7887ac97fe8_1684391112567-964673970"
  },
  "detail": "A shirt want to permission: true",
  "user_id": {
    "$oid": "635a011245faa7887ac97fe8"
  },
  "property": {
    "_type": "crew_",
    "color": "rgb(255,255,255)"
  },
  "permission": true,
  "shirtPrice": null
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6465c51ef3c94e5d47515a9c"
  },
  "nameshirt_": "Nokia 3310 Black",
  "shirt_path": {
    "front": "635a011245faa7887ac97fe8_1684391198301-40193818",
    "back": "635a011245faa7887ac97fe8_1684391198302-188066608"
  },
  "detail": "A shirt want to permission: true",
  "user_id": {
    "$oid": "635a011245faa7887ac97fe8"
  },
  "property": {
    "_type": "crew_",
    "color": "rgb(28, 28, 28)"
  },
  "permission": true,
  "shirtPrice": null
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6465c559f3c94e5d47515aa0"
  },
  "nameshirt_": "Nokia 3310 White",
  "shirt_path": {
    "front": "635a011245faa7887ac97fe8_1684391257947-1238598",
    "back": "635a011245faa7887ac97fe8_1684391257948-899007120"
  },
  "detail": "A shirt want to permission: true",
  "user_id": {
    "$oid": "635a011245faa7887ac97fe8"
  },
  "property": {
    "_type": "crew_",
    "color": "rgb(255,255,255)"
  },
  "permission": true,
  "shirtPrice": null
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6465c5d2f3c94e5d47515ab1"
  },
  "nameshirt_": "Suit",
  "shirt_path": {
    "front": "635a011245faa7887ac97fe8_1684391378485-477871643",
    "back": "635a011245faa7887ac97fe8_1684391378486-59455263"
  },
  "detail": "A shirt want to permission: true",
  "user_id": {
    "$oid": "635a011245faa7887ac97fe8"
  },
  "property": {
    "_type": "crew_",
    "color": "rgb(255, 255, 255)"
  },
  "permission": true,
  "shirtPrice": null
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6465c5f4f3c94e5d47515ab5"
  },
  "nameshirt_": "Love Black",
  "shirt_path": {
    "front": "635a011245faa7887ac97fe8_1684391412836-275305128",
    "back": "635a011245faa7887ac97fe8_1684391412836-504005671"
  },
  "detail": "A shirt want to permission: true",
  "user_id": {
    "$oid": "635a011245faa7887ac97fe8"
  },
  "property": {
    "_type": "crew_",
    "color": "rgb(28, 28, 28)"
  },
  "permission": true,
  "shirtPrice": null
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6465c609f3c94e5d47515ab9"
  },
  "nameshirt_": "Love White",
  "shirt_path": {
    "front": "635a011245faa7887ac97fe8_1684391433708-900211184",
    "back": "635a011245faa7887ac97fe8_1684391433709-449266748"
  },
  "detail": "A shirt want to permission: true",
  "user_id": {
    "$oid": "635a011245faa7887ac97fe8"
  },
  "property": {
    "_type": "crew_",
    "color": "rgb(255,255,255)"
  },
  "permission": true,
  "shirtPrice": null
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6465c650f3c94e5d47515ad4"
  },
  "nameshirt_": "Morder",
  "shirt_path": {
    "front": "63f5f7ae0702622a75fe195a_1684391504734-249871776",
    "back": "63f5f7ae0702622a75fe195a_1684391504735-687538480"
  },
  "detail": "A shirt want to permission: true",
  "user_id": {
    "$oid": "63f5f7ae0702622a75fe195a"
  },
  "property": {
    "_type": "crew_",
    "color": "rgb(255,255,255)"
  },
  "permission": true,
  "shirtPrice": null
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6465c680f3c94e5d47515ad8"
  },
  "nameshirt_": "Open Eye",
  "shirt_path": {
    "front": "63f5f7ae0702622a75fe195a_1684391552259-881844752",
    "back": "63f5f7ae0702622a75fe195a_1684391552260-145189890"
  },
  "detail": "A shirt want to permission: true",
  "user_id": {
    "$oid": "63f5f7ae0702622a75fe195a"
  },
  "property": {
    "_type": "crew_",
    "color": "rgb(28, 28, 28)"
  },
  "permission": true,
  "shirtPrice": null
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6465c6abf3c94e5d47515adc"
  },
  "nameshirt_": "No Me",
  "shirt_path": {
    "front": "63f5f7ae0702622a75fe195a_1684391595795-339541943",
    "back": "63f5f7ae0702622a75fe195a_1684391595796-1682953"
  },
  "detail": "A shirt want to permission: true",
  "user_id": {
    "$oid": "63f5f7ae0702622a75fe195a"
  },
  "property": {
    "_type": "crew_",
    "color": "rgb(255, 255, 255)"
  },
  "permission": true,
  "shirtPrice": null
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6465c883f3c94e5d47515ae3"
  },
  "nameshirt_": "ไอ้นี่โกหก",
  "shirt_path": {
    "front": "63f5f7ae0702622a75fe195a_1684392067490-597075961",
    "back": "63f5f7ae0702622a75fe195a_1684392067491-23256549"
  },
  "detail": "A shirt want to permission: true",
  "user_id": {
    "$oid": "63f5f7ae0702622a75fe195a"
  },
  "property": {
    "_type": "crew_",
    "color": "rgb(255,255,255)"
  },
  "permission": true,
  "shirtPrice": null
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6465c8c2f3c94e5d47515afc"
  },
  "nameshirt_": "Saitama OK",
  "shirt_path": {
    "front": "63f5f7ae0702622a75fe195a_1684392130629-759014719",
    "back": "63f5f7ae0702622a75fe195a_1684392130630-356822619"
  },
  "detail": "A shirt want to permission: true",
  "user_id": {
    "$oid": "63f5f7ae0702622a75fe195a"
  },
  "property": {
    "_type": "crew_",
    "color": "rgb(28, 28, 28)"
  },
  "permission": true,
  "shirtPrice": null
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6465c932f3c94e5d47515b00"
  },
  "nameshirt_": "Life cycle",
  "shirt_path": {
    "front": "63f5f7ae0702622a75fe195a_1684392242723-343824795",
    "back": "63f5f7ae0702622a75fe195a_1684392242724-738279055"
  },
  "detail": "A shirt want to permission: true",
  "user_id": {
    "$oid": "63f5f7ae0702622a75fe195a"
  },
  "property": {
    "_type": "crew_",
    "color": "rgb(255,255,255)"
  },
  "permission": true,
  "shirtPrice": null
}]